Guide to the Labor Theater Records WAG.033
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series III: Unprocessed Materials
  - NEA, Revision, Approval, and Final Report (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - NYSCA, 1982-1983 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - NYSCA, 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - NYSCA, 1981-1982 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - NEA-General (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Reviews of/and Correspondence Re: Submitted Scripts (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Screenplay Correspondence (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Letter of Support (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - AFL-CIO (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Arts and Business Council (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Arts and Education Bill (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Barre, Vermont (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Bicentennial Exchange Fellowship Report (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Charles Bukowski (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Cable TV (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Chelsea History Day (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Chelsea Neighborhood (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Dramatists' Guild (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Eleven 99 Hospital Union, Bread and Rose, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Empire State College (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Energy Special (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - English and European Contacts (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Equipment (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Fasanella (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Films (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Film Series, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Forms (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Future Projects: Debs, adamic, Ma Barker (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Foundations (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Group Theater (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Groups (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Internships (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - International Theater Institute (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Joyce Kornbluh (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Labor Studies Center (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Labor and the Humanities (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Labor Theater Community Outreach (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - League of Women Voters (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Letters of Support (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - National Congress of Neighborhood Women Class (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - New York Labor History Association (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Nott (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Office and Equipment Supplies, Photo and Reproduction Services (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Open House, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - OSHA (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Poets and Writers, Inc. (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Political Artists (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Program Resources (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Project Work (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Sally's Party, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Society of Stage Directors (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Barrie Stavis (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Subscription Campaign, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Subscription Ideas (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Theaters (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Susan B. Anthony (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - 13th Street Space (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Working New Yorkers (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Annenberg/CPB (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Benefit, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - Benefit, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Benefit, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Benefit, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Benefit, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Fundraiser, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Funding Fundraiser, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Funding Patrons and Contributors (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Marge Dahle (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Labor Theater Solicitations (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Fundraising, Direct Mail, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Brookdale Foundation (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Constitution-NEH (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Funding Ford Foundation (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - General Proposal (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Grants Class (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Funding Labor (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - "The Second Beginning" by Emanuel Fried (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - "Drop Hammer," by Emanuel Fried (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - "Elegy for Stanley Gorski," by Emanuel Fried (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Tillie Olsen reading "Hey Sailor", Oct 23, 1983 (Box 12)
  - Herbert Benjamin, BBH and Songs, Sis Cunningham, 1975 (Box 12)
  - Unprocessed films (Reel 20)
  - [Trims and outs], undated; wag033_017 (Box 17, 16mm film reels 17)
  - [Amalgamated Clothing Workers Wk Print], wag033_018 (Box 18, 16mm film reels 18)
  - [Daily], undated; wag033_019 (Box 18, 16mm film reels 19)
  - [How your Representatives voted], 1959-1986; WAG033_020 (Box 18, 16mm film reels 20)
  - [Amalgamated Clothing Workers], undated; WAG033_021 (Box 17, 16mm film reels 21)
  - [Amalgamated Clothing Workers] -- work print, 1959-1986; wag033_022 (Box 18, 16mm film reels 22)
  - [Protesting gas and electric prices], undated; wag033_023 (Box 18, 16mm film reels 23)
- Series IV: Photographs, 1970s-1980s
  Scope and Content Note
  Black and white images of various productions by the Labor Theater, and members of the casts, ca. 1970s-1980s.
  Arranged alphabetically by production name.
  - "200 RPM" (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - "A Peaceable Kingdom" (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - "Bandits" Cast, [1979] (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - "Bayside Boys" (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - "Bottom Line" (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - "C.A.S.T." Spring Tour, 1978-1984 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - "Don't Cry", undated (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - "Dying" (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - "I Just", undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - "I Just Wanted," Photos and Lists (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - "Jack London" (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - "Labor Theater in England" (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - "Left Out Lady" (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - "Men Together" (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - "Pictures and Bio's Nightshift" (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - "Power" (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - "Railroad Bill" (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - "Re-Po" (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - "Rip", undated (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - "Rip" Photos with Captions (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - "Rip Torn", undated (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - "Shared Season" (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - "Singly None", 1975 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - "Singly None" Photos and Programs (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - TLT Production (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - TLT Productions Early Shows, "Waiting for Lefty" and "Dodo Birds" (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Unidentified Performance (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - "Why I Left California" (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - "Wobblies" (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - "Workin' Our Way" (Box 13, Folder 30)